Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of United States Politics and Government Serials TAM.759
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- National Alliance: National Alliance Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1-8, Box 21, Folder 1-9, Box 22, Box 23, Folder 1-11, Box 25, Box 26, Folder 1-10, Box 27, Box 33, Folder 2-9, Box Shared Tamiment 048, Folder 1-2)
- National Boycott News: Institute for Consumer Responsibility, Seattle, WA, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- National Campaign to Impeach Nixon Newsletter: Washington National Office & Resource Center, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- National Strike Information Center: National Strike Information Center, Waltham, MA, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- NCARL DC Memo: National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 13, Folder 33)
- NDI Reports: National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- New Democrat: New Democratic Movement, Brooklyn, NY, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- New Democrat: New Democrats, Reading, MA, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- New Democratic Movement National Bulletin: New Democratic Movement National Office, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- New Dimensions: New Dimensions Magazine, Whitewater, WI, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- New Dimensions: New Dimensions, San Francisco, CA, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- New Directions: Center for American Values, La Palma, CA, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- New Federalist: The New Federalist, Leesburg, VA, 1987-1991 (Box 17, Folder 15, Box 24, Folder 1-5, Box 28, Folder 1-7, Box 29, Folder 1-6, Box 34, Folder 2-8, Box 45, Folder 4)
- New Federalist: United World Federalists, University of Chicago Chapter, Chicago, IL, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- New Jersey Peoples' Alliance Organizing Committee Alliance: New Jersey Peoples' Alliance Organizing Committee Alliance, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- New Patriot: New Patriot Alliance, Chicago, IL, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- New Patriot: Johnny Appleseed Patriotic Publications, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- New Patriot: Patriotic Majority, Chicago, IL, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- New Southerner: Donald L. West, Montgomery, AL, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- New Studies on the Left: Saxifrage Publications Group, Boulder, CO, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- New York Beacon: New York Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, New York, NY, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 22, Box 45, Folder 7)
- New York Independent Advocate, n.p., 1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- New York Review of Sex & Politics: New York Feed, Co., New York, NY, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- New York State Peace and Freedom Party Campaign Platform: NY Peace and Freedom Party, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- News and Views: National Coalition to Ban Handguns, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- News from The Road: Make the Road by Walking, Inc., Brooklyn, NY, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- News Liberal Party of New York State: Liberal Party of New York State, New York, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
- News of the Week: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- News Update: Coalition on Government Spying, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Newsletter: Citizens for Kennedy-Fulbright, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Newsletter: Council of Economic Priorities, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Newsletter: New Movement in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence, Chicago, IL, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- NICWOMEN: National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- No Uncertain Times: U.S. Terms Limits, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- North American Operations Bulletin: U.S. Labor Party, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 14-16)
- North Georgia Review: A Magazine of the Southern Regions: North Georgia Review, Clayton, GA, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Northern Light: Washington Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, Seattle, WA, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Northern Star: Aurora Publications, Inc., Hartford, CT, 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10-12)
- Notes from the Empire State Peace and Freedom Party: n.p., 1969 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Noticias Del Centro News: Centro de Estudios Puertorriquenos, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Nueva lucha: Partido Socialista Puertorriqueno, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- NY SDA News-Letter: New York Students for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- NY State SDA Reporter: New York Region of Students for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- NYANA News: New York Association for New Americans, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- NYS ADA: Americans for Democratic Action, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Obreros en Marcha: M.I.N.P.-El Comite, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Observation Post: Observation Post, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- One Spark Can Start A Prairie Fire!: Impeach Nixon Campaign, Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Organizing Committee Newsletter: Federation for Progress, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Orono Free Press: Orono Free Press, Orono, ME, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Outside the Net: Outside the Net, Lansing, MI, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35, Box 18, Folder 15-16)
- Overseas Press Bulletin: The Overseas Press Club of America, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Partido Obrero Liberador: Partido Obrero Liberador, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- People and Taxes: Tax Reform Research Group, Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- People for a New System: Industrial Union Party, Red Bank, NJ, 1992-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Peoples' Alliance Coordinators Update: Peoples' Alliance, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- PJEC newsletter: Rochester Peace and Justice Center, Inc., Rochester, NY, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Plain Talk: Plain Talk Publishing Association, Salt Lake City, UT, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Plenum Reports: Plenum Reports, USA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Poder Estudiantil: Federacion de Universitarios Pro Independencia, Rio Piedras, Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Poland of Today: Monthly Bulletin of Information: Library of the Polish Embassy Publishing Office, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Polish Review: Polish Review Publishing Co., New York, NY, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Political Action: NY State American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Political Resolution of the Founding Convention: Revolutionary Socialist League, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Political Week: Political Week, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Prensa Popular: Prensa Popular, San Diego, CA, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Prevailing Winds: Prevailing Winds Research, Santa Barbara, CA, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Prevailing Winds: Center for the Preservation of Modern History, Santa Barbara, CA, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Pro-Democracy Organizer: Equal Rights Congress, Chicago, IL, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- PROBE: PROBE, Culver City, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Professional: Professionals' Coalition for Nuclear..., Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Progressive Advocate: Progressive Party of Illinois, Chicago, IL, 1925 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Progressive Agenda: Center for Democratic Alternatives, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Progressive Populist: Ampersand Publishing Company, Storm Lake, IA, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
- Progressive Review: The Progressive Review, Washington, DC, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Propaganda Analysis: Institute for Propaganda Analysis, Inc., New York, NY, 1938-1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- PTS: Peoples Translation Service, Berkeley, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Public Eye: Repression Information Project, Washington, DC, 1977-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6, Folder 13)
- Public Interest Economics: Public Interest Economics Foundation, Washington, DC, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Public Interest Letter: Center for Science in the Public Interest, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Public Life: Federation for Participatory Democracy, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Public Life: The Public Life, New York, NY, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 4, Box 45, Folder 19)
- Pueblo: Partido Comunista Puertorriqueno, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico Update / Puerto Rico Al Dia: US/Puerto Rico Solidarity Network, Bronx, NY, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
- Radical Folk: Radical Folk, Valdez, NM, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Ray O. Light: Ray O. Light, Boston, MA, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Reagan Watch: The First 100 Days: Americans for Democratic Action, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Real Press: Real Press, Evanston, IL, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Rebel: Rebel Inc., College Park, GA, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Red Bass: Red Bass Productions, Inc., New Orleans, LA, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Red Times: Youth Against War and Fascism, Detroit, MI, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Relevant: Committees of Correspondence Youth, San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Report from Washington: American Committee for the Protection of Foreign Born, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Report of the Proceedings of the Third Conference for Progressive Political Action: CPPA, St. Louis, MO, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Reporter: Fortnightly Publishing Co., New York, NY, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Resistance: Journal of Grassroots Direct Action: Liberation Collective, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Rev News: Chicago Revolutionary Network (CHIREVNET), Chicago, IL, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Review: Review, New Brunswick, NJ, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Review of Politics: University of Notre Dame Press, Notre Dame, IN, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Revolution Youth!: Solidarity, Detroit, MI, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Revolutionary Youth Movement: Revolutionary Youth Movement, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10, Box Shared Tamiment 063, Folder 11)
- Right-Wing Watch: People for the American Way, Washington, DC, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Rojo Negro: Secretario de Correspondencia y Publicaciones MPI, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Roman Forum: Associated Forums, Ltd., Los Angeles, CA, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Interview: San Francisco Interview, San Francisco, CA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- San Francisco Peace and Freedom Party Newsletter: San Francisco Peace and Freedom Party, San Francisco, CA, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Sanders Scoop: Sanders Scoop, Burlington, VT, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Science and Public Affairs - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists: Education Foundation for Nuclear Science, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Seize the Times!: Revolutionary Student Brigade, Chicago, IL, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Siembra: National Puerto Rican Left Movement (MINP-El Comite), New York, NY, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Smirk: Schiz-flux, USA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- SNAFU: SNAFU, New York, NY, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Social Ecology News: Institute for Social Ecology, Plainfield, VT, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- South Manhattan Peace and Freedom Report: South Manhattan Peace and Freedom Party, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17, Box 45, Folder 20)
- Southern Advocate: Equal Rights Congress, Atlanta, GA, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Southern Frontier: Southern Regional Council, Inc, Atlanta, GA, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Space and Security News: Institute for Space and Security Studies, Potomac, MD, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Spotlight for the Nation: Committee for Constitutional Government, Inc., New York, NY, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Spotlight on Economy in Government: Cordite Fidelity Company, Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Spotlight: A Report on the Smith Act Trials: Spotlight, Detroit, MI, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- SSOC Bulletin: Southern Student Organizing Committee, Nashville, TN, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Student Federalist: Student Federalist, Washington, D.C., 1944 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 5)
- Tax News & Notes: National Committee on Tax Justice, Washington, DC, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Tax Strike News: Tax Strike News, Porterville, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Tell it to Hanoi: Young Americans for Freedom, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- The BSRL newsletter: Bank for Socially Responsible Lending Organizing Group, Brooklyn, NY, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "the whole damn pie shop": New Indicator Collective, San Diego, CA, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Theory & Practice: Theory & Practice, Los Angeles, CA, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- They Are Freedom Fighters Not Terrorists: National Committee, Chicago, IL, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Throw the Bum Out!: Workers Committee to Throw the Bum Out, New York, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Till Eulenspiegel: Till Eulenspiegel, Chicago, IL, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Time Machine: The Time Machine, Beckly, WV, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Times of the Americas: Times of the Americas, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Tip of the Iceberg: Committee for the Suit Against Government Misconduct, New York, NY, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Towards a Democratic Majority: Peace Politics, Santa Ana, CA, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Trumpet of Conscience: Concerned Citizens United, Durham, NC, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Turn our Country Around!: Committees of Correspondence, New York, NY, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- U.S.A.: Alice Widener / USA Publishing Company, Inc., New York, NY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- UCDAF Bulletin: Committee for the Defense of Academic Freedom, Washington, DC, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- United States Anti-Imperialist League: United States Anti-Imperialist League, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Unity/La Unidad: League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), New York, NY, Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Update: Committee for the Suit Against Government Misconduct, New York, NY, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Update for Better Living: State University of New York, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bath, NY, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Update on Congress: National Committee to Preserve..., Washington, DC, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Upstream: Feoh Rune of the Quail Club, Lawrence, KS, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Upsurge: Anti-Imperialist League of the US, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- URISA 25th Annual Conference (conference proceedings): Urban and Regional Information Systems Association, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- US and Revolution: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, CA, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- US-Cuba Bulletin: Cuban-American Committee for Normalization of Relations with Cuba, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Venceremos: Venceremos, Ann Arbor, MI, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Vida del Partido: Partido Comunista Puertorriqueno, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Vieques Update: Vieques Historical Archives and the US/Puerto Rico Solidarity Network, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Vietnam Veterans Against the War: VVAW-WSO National Prison Project, Chicago, IL, circa 1960s (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 6)
- Vita Wa Watu (More Notes from a New Afrikan POW Journal): Cooperative Distribution Service, Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Vital Information: Vital Information, New Orleans, LA, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Voter Express: DNC / Rainbow Coalition, New York, NY, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Voting and Democracy Review: Center for Voting and Democracy, Washington, DC, 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Wallace Labor Action: The Wallace Campaign, Montgomery, AL, Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Washington and You: Washington and You, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Washington Letter: American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, Educational and Legislative Office, Washington, DC, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Washington Newsletter: Friends Committee on National Legislation, Washington, DC, 1956-1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Washington Observer: Kwang Neun Hahn, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Washington Observer Newsletter: American Mercury, Torrance, CA, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Washington Watch: Washington Watch, Inc., Lansing, MI, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Ways & Means: National Center for Policy Alternatives, Washington, DC, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- WF News: Working Families Party, Brooklyn, NY, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- What We Believe: Social Democrats, USA, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Where It's At...: San Francisco Peace & Freedom Party Independent Caucus, San Francisco, CA, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Witness: Fellowship of Reconciliation, Nyack, NY, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Woman Constitutionalist: Women for Constitutional Government, Mount Kisco, NY, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Working Families News: Working Families Party, Brooklyn, NY, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Worklist Mailing: Southern Student Organizing Committee, Nashville, TN, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Y.L.O.: Young Lords Association, New York, NY, circa 1960s (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 7)
- YAWF Newsletter: Youth Against War & Fascism, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Youth in Focus: DARE, Direct Action for Rights and Equality, Providence, RI, 1993 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 8)
- Youth Get Organised: ILRIG (International Labour Resource and Information Group), Cape Town, South Africa, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Youth News: Youth News, Brooklyn, NY, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Youth Rising: Youth Liberation, USA, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 17, Box 19, Folder 9)
- Zeta Magazine: The Institute for Social and Cultural Change, Boston, MA, 1987-1997 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
- Zippie!: Youth International Party, USA, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)